Guide to the The New Leader Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: Photographs, 1906-2005, undated
  - Jaruzelski, Wojciech--Polish Defense Minister, 1981-2001, undated (Box 182, Folder 94)
  - Jaspers, Karl, undated (Box 182, Folder 95)
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1968-1971, undated (Box 182, Folder 96)
  - Jebb, Sir Gladwyn, 1956, undated (Box 182, Folder 97)
  - Jefferson, Thomas, 1930 (Box 182, Folder 98)
  - Jenkins, Roy, 1967-1980, undated (Box 182, Folder 99)
  - Jenner, Wm. E., 1950, undated (Box 182, Folder 100)
  - Jessup, Philip, undated (Box 182, Folder 101)
  - Jesus, Jose-Luis, undated (Box 182, Folder 102)
  - Jiang Zemin, 1995 (Box 182, Folder 103)
  - Jibril, Ahmed, 1983 (Box 182, Folder 104)
  - Jiminez, Capt. Antonio Nunez, 1959 (Box 182, Folder 105)
  - Jiminez, Marcos Perez, 1953-1958 (Box 182, Folder 106)
  - Jinnah, Mohammed Ali, undated (Box 182, Folder 107)
  - Jobert, Michel, 1974 (Box 182, Folder 108)
  - John, Dr. Otto, undated (Box 182, Folder 109)
  - Johnson, Pres. Andrew, 1868, 1960 (Box 182, Folder 110)
  - Johnson, Gen. Harold, 1964 (Box 182, Folder 111)
  - Johnson, Louis, undated (Box 182, Folder 112)
  - Johnson, Lyndon, 1954-1968, undated (Box 182, Folder 113)
  - Johnson, Lyndon--Foreign Leaders, 1961-1967 (Box 182, Folder 114)
  - Johnson, Nicholas, 1964 (Box 182, Folder 115)
  - Johnston, Eric, 1951-1952, undated (Box 182, Folder 116)
  - Johnston, W.H., undated (Box 182, Folder 117)
  - Joint Chiefs of Staff, 1950-1957, undated (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Joliot-Curie, Frederic, 1948-1950 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Jones, Bobby, 1953 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Jonsson, Emil, undated (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Jordan--Scenes, 1958, 1970, undated (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, Barbara, 1972-1974, undated (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Jordan, Hamilton, 1976-1977 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, Vernon, 1971-1978 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Jowitt, Earl, undated (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Joxe, Louis, 1961-1962 (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Joy, Admiral Charles Turner, 1951 (Box 183, Folder 11)
  - Juan Carlos, Prince, 1954-1977 (Box 183, Folder 12)
  - Juan, Don, 1946-1964, undated (Box 183, Folder 13)
  - Judd, Walter H., undated (Box 183, Folder 14)
  - Juin, Marshal Alphonse, 1951-1952, undated (Box 183, Folder 15)
  - Jumblat, Kamal, 1976 (Junblat, Kamal) (Box 183, Folder 16)
  - Juvenile Delinquents, 1950-1958 (Box 183, Folder 17)
  - Kadar, Janos, 1960-1985 (Box 183, Folder 18)
  - Kaddoumi, Farouk, 1976 (Box 183, Folder 19)
  - Kaganovich, Lazarus, 1955 (Box 183, Folder 20)
  - Kahane, Meir, 1984 (Box 183, Folder 21)
  - Kahn, Albert, undated (Box 183, Folder 22)
  - Kahn, Alfred, 1977-1979 (Box 183, Folder 23)
  - Kahn, Herman, 1961-1968 (Box 183, Folder 24)
  - Kalleu, Dr. Horace, undated (Box 183, Folder 25)
  - Kameneu, Leo, undated (Box 183, Folder 26)
  - Kamp, Joseph P., 1950 (Box 183, Folder 27)
  - Kampelman, Max, 1991, undated (Box 183, Folder 28)
  - Kampman, Viggo, 1955-1960 (Box 183, Folder 29)
  - Kangxi, undated (Box 183, Folder 30)
  - Karnia, Stanislaw--Polish Comm. Party Leader, 1980, undated (Box 183, Folder 31)
  - Kantor, Tadeusz, undated (Box 183, Folder 32)
  - Kapitonov, Ivan V., 1971 (Box 183, Folder 33)
  - Kappler, Herbert, 1947 (Box 183, Folder 34)
  - Kaplan, Eliezer, undated (Box 183, Folder 35)
  - Karadzic, Radouan, 1993 (Box 183, Folder 36)
  - Karamanlis, Constantine, 1957-1959 (Box 183, Folder 37)
  - Karume, 1964 (Box 183, Folder 38)
  - Kardeli, Eduard, 1946-1974 (Box 183, Folder 39)
  - Kashani, Ayatollah, undated (Box 183, Folder 40)
  - Kashmir--Scenes, 1947-1965 (Box 183, Folder 41)
  - Kassem, Abdul Karim El, 1958-1959 (Box 183, Folder 42)
  - El-Kassouny, Abdel, 1959 (Box 183, Folder 43)
  - Katz, Milton, 1950 (Box 183, Folder 44)
  - Pres. Katzur, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 45)
  - Kaufman, Judge Irving, 1971 (Box 183, Folder 46)
  - Kaunda, Kenneth, 1961-1979 (Box 183, Folder 47)
  - Kawakawi, Jotaro, undated (Box 183, Folder 48)
  - Kawilarang, Col., 1955 (Box 183, Folder 49)
  - Kean, Thomas, undated (Box 183, Folder 50)
  - Kecskemeti, Paul, undated (Box 183, Folder 51)
  - Kefauver, Estes, 1951, undated (Box 183, Folder 52)
  - Keitel, Wilhelm, 1946, undated (Box 183, Folder 53)
  - Kellen, Konrad, undated (Box 183, Folder 54)
  - Kekkonen, Urho, 1961, undated (Box 183, Folder 55)
  - Kemp, Jack, 1978, 1980, undated (Box 183, Folder 56)
  - Kennard, William, 1998-2000 (Box 183, Folder 57)
  - Kennan, George F., 1957-1967, undated (Box 183, Folder 58)
  - Kennedy, David M., 1969 (Box 183, Folder 59)
  - Kennedy, Howard, undated (Box 183, Folder 60)
  - JFK assassination, 1963-1964, undated (Box 183, Folder 61)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1962-1982, undated (Box 183, Folder 62)
  - Kennedy, Jack, 1960-1962, undated (Box 183, Folder 63)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P., 1960-1961, undated (Box 183, Folder 64)
  - Kennedy, Robert, 1960-1968, undated (Box 183, Folder 65)
  - Kennedy, W.P., undated (Box 183, Folder 66)
  - Kenya, 1952-1985, undated (Box 183, Folder 67)
  - Kenyatta, Charles, 1967 (Box 183, Folder 68)
  - Kenyatta, Jomo--Kenya--Nationalist Leader, 1952-1961 (Box 183, Folder 69)
  - Kerensky, Alexander, 1950 (Box 183, Folder 70)
  - Kerr, Clark, 1946-1958 (Box 183, Folder 71)
  - Kerr, Senator Robert, 1957-1963 (Box 183, Folder 72)
  - Keynes, Lord John Marnard, 1941-1946 (Box 183, Folder 73)
  - Keyserling, Leon, 1949-1955 (Box 183, Folder 74)
  - Khaddan, Abdul Halim, 1975 (Box 183, Folder 75)
  - Khalaf, Kareem, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 76)
  - Khan, Liaquat Ali, 1950 (Box 183, Folder 77)
  - Khan, Gen. Mohammed Ayub, 1958-1965 (Box 183, Folder 78)
  - Khan, Mohammed Zafrullah, 1962, undated (Box 183, Folder 79)
  - Khan, Sadruddin Aga, 1988 (Box 183, Folder 80)
  - Khatib, Ruhi El, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 81)
  - Kheel, Theodore, undated (Box 183, Folder 82)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita S., 1955-1991, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 183, Folder 83 to 84)
  - Khyber Pass, undated (Box 183, Folder 85)
  - Kiesinger, Kurt, 1967-1969 (Box 183, Folder 86)
  - Kilgore, Harley M., undated (Box 183, Folder 87)
  - Killingsworth, Charles C., 1952 (Box 183, Folder 88)
  - Kim Dae-Jung, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 89)
  - Kim Il Sung, 1950-1968 (Box 183, Folder 90)
  - Kim Jae-Kyu, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 91)
  - Kim Jong Pil, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 92)
  - Kim Young-Sam, 1975, 1995 (Box 183, Folder 93)
  - Kimball, Daniel, 1949 (Box 183, Folder 94)
  - Kimpton, Lawrence A., undated (Box 183, Folder 95)
  - King Khaled, 1975-1978, undated (Box 183, Folder 96)
  - King, Rev. Martin Luther, 1956-1964 (Box 183, Folder 97)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Funeral, 1968 (Box 183, Folder 98)
  - Kingsley, J. Donald, undated (Box 183, Folder 99)
  - Kinkel, Klaus, 1995 (Box 183, Folder 100)
  - Kinnock, Neil, 1984, undated (Box 183, Folder 101)
  - Kirchway, Freda, undated (Box 183, Folder 102)
  - Kirilenko, Andrei P., 1971, undated (Box 183, Folder 103)
  - Kirk, Alan, 1944-1951 (Box 183, Folder 104)
  - Kirk, Norman, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 105)
  - Kirk, Paul Jr., 1985, 1987 (Box 183, Folder 106)
  - Kirkland, Lane, 1972, 1987, undated (Box 183, Folder 107)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane, 1981 (Box 183, Folder 108)
  - Kishi, Nobusuke, 1957-1959 (Box 183, Folder 109)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1966-1983, undated (Box 183, Folder 110)
  - Kittikachorn, Thanom, 1966-1968 (Box 183, Folder 111)
  - Klebanov, Vladimir, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 112)
  - Klein, Arthur G., undated (Box 183, Folder 113)
  - Klein, Herb, 1969-1970 (Box 183, Folder 114)
  - Kleisf, Heinrich Von, 1983 (Box 183, Folder 115)
  - Klestil, Thomas, 1995 (Austria) (Box 183, Folder 116)
  - Klieforth, Alexander, undated (Box 183, Folder 117)
  - Kline, Allan B., undated (Box 183, Folder 118)
  - Knight, Gov. Goodwin, 1954, undated (Box 183, Folder 119)
  - Knight, O.A., 1952, undated (Box 183, Folder 120)
  - Knowland, William F., 1951-1954, undated (Box 183, Folder 121)
  - Koch, Edward, 1992 (Box 183, Folder 122)
  - Kociolek, Stanislaw, undated (Box 183, Folder 123)
  - Koerner, Theodor, undated (Box 183, Folder 124)
  - Kohl, Helmut, 1969-1983 (Box 183, Folder 125)
  - Kohler, Foy D., undated (Box 183, Folder 126)
  - Koirala, B.P., 1959-1960 (Box 183, Folder 127)
  - Koje, undated (Box 183, Folder 128)
  - Komar, Waclaw, undated (Box 183, Folder 129)
  - Komer, Robert W., 1966 (Box 183, Folder 130)
  - Konev, Ivan, 1955, undated (Box 183, Folder 131)
  - Korea--South, 1950-1980, undated (Box 183, Folder 132)
  - Korea War Scenes, 1950-1968, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 183, Folder 133 to 134)
  - Korprulu, Fuat, 1952 (Box 183, Folder 135)
  - Koslov, Frol, 1959, 1961 (Box 183, Folder 136)
  - Kosygin, Alexei, 1963-1979, undated (Box 183, Folder 137)
  - Kotelawala, Sir John, undated (Box 183, Folder 138)
  - Kouhaux, Leon, undated (Box 183, Folder 139)
  - Koyama, Ryaji, 1956 (Box 183, Folder 140)
  - Kramer, Chas., undated (Box 183, Folder 141)
  - Kravchenko, Victor, 1949 (Box 183, Folder 142)
  - Kravchuk, Leonid M., 1991 (Box 183, Folder 143)
  - Kreisky, Bruno, 1975-1977 (Box 183, Folder 144)
  - Kreps, Juanita, 1976 (Box 183, Folder 145)
  - Krim, Belkassem, 1958 (Box 183, Folder 146)
  - Krishnamachari, Shri T.T., 1957 (Box 183, Folder 147)
  - Krishna Menon, 1955-1961 (Box 183, Folder 148)
  - Kristol, Irving, undated (Box 183, Folder 149)
  - Kruel, Armany, 1964 (Box 183, Folder 150)
  - Krutch, Joseph Wood, undated (Box 183, Folder 151)
  - Kubitschek, Juscelino, 1955-1964 (Box 183, Folder 152)
  - Ku Klux Klan, 1939-1987 (Box 183, Folder 153)
  - Kulakov, Fyodr D., 1971 (Box 183, Folder 154)
  - Kulikov, Viktor, 1972, undated (Box 183, Folder 155)
  - Kumaraswami, Kamaraj, 1963 (Box 183, Folder 156)
  - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, 1941 (Box 183, Folder 157)
  - Kuron, Jacek, undated (Box 183, Folder 158)
  - Kuwatly, Shukri Al, 1956-1957, undated (Box 183, Folder 159)
  - Kuzbari, Mahmoud, 1961 (Box 183, Folder 160)
  - Kuznetson, Anatoly, 1967 (Box 183, Folder 161)
  - Kuwait, 1948-1991 (Box 183, Folder 162)
  - Ky, Nguyen Cao, 1966-1970 (Box 183, Folder 163)
  - Kyprianou, Spyros, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 164)
  - Labor--Strike Scenes--Sweatshops and Illegal Aliens, 1969-1975, undated (Box 183, Folder 165)
  - Labouisse, Henry R., undated (Box 183, Folder 166)
  - Lacenda, Carlos, 1962-1964 (Box 183, Folder 167)
  - Lacoste, Robert, 1955, undated (Box 183, Folder 168)
  - Ladgham, Bahi, 1958 (Box 183, Folder 169)
  - Laffer, Arthur, undated (Box 183, Folder 170)
  - La Gaillarde, Pierre, 1960, undated (Box 183, Folder 171)
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello, 1934-1943 (Box 183, Folder 172)
  - Laird, Cong. Melvin, 1968-1970 (Box 183, Folder 173)
  - La Malfa, Ugo, undated (Box 183, Folder 174)
  - Lamm, Dick, undated (Box 183, Folder 175)
  - Lamont, Corliss, undated (Box 183, Folder 176)
  - Lance, Bert, 1973-1977, undated (Box 183, Folder 177)
  - Land, Thomas, undated (Box 183, Folder 178)
  - Landis, James, 1960-1961 (Box 183, Folder 179)
  - Landrum, Phil, 1959, undated (Box 183, Folder 180)
  - Lane, Lord Chief Justice G.B., 1980-1987 (Box 183, Folder 181)
  - Lange, Halvard, undated (Box 183, Folder 182)
  - Lange, Oscar, 1945-1948 (Box 183, Folder 183)
  - Langer, William, 1954, undated (Box 183, Folder 184)
  - Laniel, Joseph, undated (Box 183, Folder 185)
  - Lansdale, Edward G., 1965-1966 (Box 183, Folder 186)
  - Laos--Individuals, 1960-1974 (Box 183, Folder 187)
  - Laos--Military, 1959-1971, undated (Box 183, Folder 188)
  - Laos--Scenes, 1959-1974, undated (Box 183, Folder 189)
  - Lapie, Pierre Olivier, 1949 (Box 183, Folder 190)
  - Lapp, Dr. Ralph, undated (Box 183, Folder 191)
  - Laqueur, William Z., undated (Box 183, Folder 192)
  - Larrant, Jean, undated (Box 183, Folder 193)
  - Larrazabal, Rear Adm. Wolfgang, 1958, undated (Box 183, Folder 194)
  - Lasky, Melvin J., 1948, undated (Box 183, Folder 195)
  - Lasso, Galo Plaza, undated (Box 183, Folder 196)
  - Latin America, 1957-1963, undated (Box 183, Folder 197)
  - Lattimore, Owen, 1950-1952, undated (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Lattre de Tassigny, Gen. Juan de, undated (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Latvia scenes, 1964, undated (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Laurel, Wose P., undated (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Lausche, Frank P., 1957, undated (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Lavie, Naphtali, 1985, undated (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Law, undated (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Lawrence, David, undated (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Laxalt, Paul, 1980, undated (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Leader, George M., undated (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - League of Women Voters--Vicki Lowell, 1954-1976 (Box 184, Folder 11)
  - Leary, Howard, 1966 (Box 184, Folder 12)
  - Leber, George, 1975, undated (Box 184, Folder 13)
  - Lebanaon--Scenes, 1958-1983, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 184, Folder 14 to 15)
  - Lecanvet, Jean, 1955-1965 (Box 184, Folder 16)
  - Lechin, Juan, 1961 (Box 184, Folder 17)
  - Lee, J. Bracken, undated (Box 184, Folder 18)
  - Lee, Capt. Kong, 1960, undated (Box 184, Folder 19)
  - Lee, Richard C., 1959-1966 (Box 184, Folder 20)
  - Lehman, Herbert H., 1950, undated (Box 184, Folder 21)
  - Lenin, Vladimir, 1982, undated (Box 184, Folder 22)
  - Lennon, Sen. Alton A., 1954 (Box 184, Folder 23)
  - Leone, Giovanni, 1968-1978 (Box 184, Folder 24)
  - Leopold, King, undated (Box 184, Folder 25)
  - Le Sage, Jean--Premier of Quebec, 1961 (Box 184, Folder 26)
  - Lesisnski, John, 1949 (Box 184, Folder 27)
  - Le Troquer, Andre, 1958 (Box 184, Folder 28)
  - Lev, Leon, undated (Box 184, Folder 29)
  - Lever, Harold, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 30)
  - Levesque, Rene, 1969-1980 (Box 184, Folder 31)
  - Levin, Carl, 1979 (Box 184, Folder 32)
  - Levinger, Rabbi Moshe, 1984 (Box 184, Folder 33)
  - Levitas and Josephson, 1958, undated (Box 184, Folder 34)
  - Lewis, John, 1998 (Box 184, Folder 35)
  - Lewis, Wohn L., 1936-1951 (Box 184, Folder 36)
  - Lewis, W. Arthur, undated (Box 184, Folder 37)
  - Liaquat, Ali Kahn, 1950, undated (Box 184, Folder 38)
  - Libby, Willard, 1954-1960 (Box 184, Folder 39)
  - Liberia, 1947-1956 (Box 184, Folder 40)
  - Libya, undated (Box 184, Folder 41)
  - Lichenstein, Charles M.., 1983 (Box 184, Folder 42)
  - Licht, Frank, undated (Box 184, Folder 43)
  - Lie, Trygve, 1946-1949, undated (Box 184, Folder 44)
  - Lilienthal, David, 1949-1950, undated (Box 184, Folder 45)
  - Limb, Ben C., 1950, undated (Box 184, Folder 46)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, undated (Box 184, Folder 47)
  - Lincoln Memorial, 1954-1955, undated (Box 184, Folder 48)
  - Lindsay, John, 1965-1969 (Box 184, Folder 49)
  - Lingappa, Vishwanath, undated (Box 184, Folder 50)
  - Lini, Walter, 1976-1981 (Box 184, Folder 51)
  - Linowitz, Sol, undated (Box 184, Folder 52)
  - Lipper, Eleanor, undated (Box 184, Folder 53)
  - Lis, Bogdan, undated (Box 184, Folder 54)
  - List, Kurt, undated (Box 184, Folder 55)
  - Litvinov, Maxim, 1942, undated (Box 184, Folder 56)
  - Liv Shao Chi, 1964-1966 (Box 184, Folder 57)
  - Livingston, David, 1948 (Box 184, Folder 58)
  - Lhasa, 1974 (Box 184, Folder 59)
  - Lieras, Alberto, 1956-1957, undated (Box 184, Folder 60)
  - Lloyd, Selwyn, 1959, undated (Box 184, Folder 61)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1949-1964, undated (Box 184, Folder 62)
  - Lodge, John Davis, undated (Box 184, Folder 63)
  - Long, Oliver, 1973 (Box 184, Folder 64)
  - Long, Gov. Earl, 1948, undated (Box 184, Folder 65)
  - Long, Russell, 1955-1978 (Box 184, Folder 66)
  - Longo, Luigi, 1947-1969, undated (Box 184, Folder 67)
  - Lon Nol, 1970 (Box 184, Folder 68)
  - Longshoremen, 1953-1959, undated (Box 184, Folder 69)
  - Lopez-Mateos, Adolfo, 1958-1959, undated (Box 184, Folder 70)
  - Lott, Gen. Henrique T., 1955 (Box 184, Folder 71)
  - Loufti, Omar, 1956 (Box 184, Folder 72)
  - Louis XIV, undated (Box 184, Folder 73)
  - Lovett, Robert A., undated (Box 184, Folder 74)
  - Lowery, Joseph, 1972-1979 (Box 184, Folder 75)
  - Lubell, S., 1955 (Box 184, Folder 76)
  - Lubke, Heinrich, 1963-1964, undated (Box 184, Folder 77)
  - Lucas, Scott, 1949, undated (Box 184, Folder 78)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, 1953, undated (Box 184, Folder 79)
  - Luce, Charles F., 1971-1974 (Box 184, Folder 80)
  - Lucy, Autherine, 1956 (Box 184, Folder 81)
  - Luczywo, Helena, undated (Box 184, Folder 82)
  - Ludendorff, undated (Box 184, Folder 83)
  - Luder, Italo, 1983 (Box 184, Folder 84)
  - Luebke, Heinrich, 1959 (Box 184, Folder 85)
  - Lukacs, Gyorgy, 1968-1970 (Box 184, Folder 86)
  - Lundine, Stanley N., 1976 (Box 184, Folder 87)
  - Luns, Joseph, 1978 (Box 184, Folder 88)
  - Luxembourg--Scenes, 1952-1977, undated (Box 184, Folder 89)
  - Lynd, Staughton, undated (Box 184, Folder 90)
  - Lysenko, Trofim, undated (Box 184, Folder 91)
  - Lyttleton, Oliver, undated (Box 184, Folder 92)
  - Macapagal, Tosadado, 1961-1963 (Box 184, Folder 93)
  - Macarthur, Douglas, 1949-1961, undated (Box 184, Folder 94)
  - Macdonald, David, 1953-1955 (Box 184, Folder 95)
  - MacEachen, Allen, 1978 (Box 184, Folder 96)
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1945-1947 (Box 184, Folder 97)
  - Macleod, Iain, 1959-1961 (Box 184, Folder 98)
  - Macmillan, Sir Harold, 1955-1960, undated (Box 184, Folder 99)
  - Madariaga, Salvador de, 1938-1949 (Box 184, Folder 100)
  - Maddox, Lester, 1961 (Box 184, Folder 101)
  - Madison, James, undated (Box 184, Folder 102)
  - Madrid Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 184, Folder 103)
  - Magnuson, Sen. Warren G., undated (Box 184, Folder 104)
  - Magsaysay, Ramon, 1952 (Box 184, Folder 105)
  - Mahoney, David, 1968-1972 (Box 184, Folder 106)
  - Mai Van Bo, 1968 (Box 184, Folder 107)
  - Maisky, Ivan, undated (Box 184, Folder 108)
  - Major, John, 1995 (Box 184, Folder 109)
  - Makarios, Archbishop, 1974-1976, undated (Box 184, Folder 110)
  - Malan, Dr. Daniel, 1948-1949, undated (Box 184, Folder 111)
  - Malaya--Scenes, 1948-1963 (Box 184, Folder 112)
  - Maldive Islands, undated (Box 184, Folder 113)
  - Malenkov, George, 1949-1957, undated (Box 184, Folder 114)
  - Mali Federation, 1959 (Box 184, Folder 115)
  - Malik, Adam, 1966 (Box 184, Folder 116)
  - Malik, Jacob, 1950 (Box 184, Folder 117)
  - Malone, George W., undated (Box 184, Folder 118)
  - Malraux, Andre, 1945-1959 (Box 184, Folder 119)
  - Maluf, Paulo Salim, 1982 (Box 184, Folder 120)
  - Manatt, Charles T., 1982-1983 (Box 184, Folder 121)
  - Manigat, 1987 (Box 184, Folder 122)
  - Manley, John, undated (Box 184, Folder 123)
  - Manley, Michael, 1976-1977 (Box 184, Folder 124)
  - Mann, Erika, undated (Box 184, Folder 125)
  - Mann, Thomas C., 1960, 1963 (Box 184, Folder 126)
  - Mannion, Clarence, 1952-1953 (Box 184, Folder 127)
  - Mansfield, Mike, 1950-1975 (Box 184, Folder 128)
  - Manteuffel, Hasson Von, undated (Box 184, Folder 129)
  - Mao Tse-Tung, 1954-1976, undated (Box 184, Folder 130)
  - Marchi, John, 1969 (Box 184, Folder 131)
  - Marcantonio, Vito, 1949, undated (Box 184, Folder 132)
  - Marchais, Georges, 1972-1978 (Box 184, Folder 133)
  - Marcos, Ferdinand and Imelda, 1973-1975 (Box 184, Folder 134)
  - Marin, Munoz Luis, 1961-1964, undated (Box 184, Folder 135)
  - Mark, Hans, 1979-1980 (Box 184, Folder 136)
  - Marshall, Burke, 1962-1963 (Box 184, Folder 137)
  - Markfield, Wallace, undated (Box 184, Folder 138)
  - Marshall, George C., 1948-1950, undated (Box 184, Folder 139)
  - Marshall Plan, 1949, undated (Box 184, Folder 140)
  - Marshall, Ray, 1976-1978 (Box 184, Folder 141)
  - Marshall, Thurgood, 1957-1972 (Box 184, Folder 142)
  - Martin, Joseph W., 1956, undated (Box 184, Folder 143)
  - Martin, William McChesney, undated (Box 184, Folder 144)
  - Martin, Paul, undated (Box 184, Folder 145)
  - Marty, Andre, undated (Box 184, Folder 146)
  - Marx, Karl, undated (Box 184, Folder 147)
  - Masaryk, Jan, undated (Box 184, Folder 148)
  - Masaryk, Thomas G., undated (Box 184, Folder 149)
  - Massing, Hede, 1951, undated (Box 184, Folder 150)
  - Massu, Gen. Jacques, 1958, undated (Box 184, Folder 151)
  - Mateos, Adolfo Lopez, 1958-1962 (Box 184, Folder 152)
  - Matheson, Scott, 1984 (Box 184, Folder 153)
  - Mathews, Elbert G., 1959 (Box 184, Folder 154)
  - Matak, Sirik, 1970 (Box 184, Folder 155)
  - Mathias, Charles, 1971-1973 (Box 184, Folder 156)
  - Matik, Jacob, 1946-1956, undated (Box 184, Folder 157)
  - Mattarella, Bernardo, 1957 (Box 184, Folder 158)
  - Matthews, Francis, undated (Box 184, Folder 159)
  - Matusow, Harvey, 1952-1954, undated (Box 184, Folder 160)
  - Mau, Vu Van, 1964 (Box 184, Folder 161)
  - Maudling, Reginald, 1955-1963 (Box 184, Folder 162)
  - Mauroy, Pierre, undated (Box 184, Folder 163)
  - Maw, Herbert, 1947 (Box 184, Folder 164)
  - Maybank, Sen. Burnet, 1952 (Box 184, Folder 165)
  - Mayer, Daniel, 1945 (Box 184, Folder 166)
  - Mayer, Jean, 1969 (Box 184, Folder 167)
  - Mayhew, Patrick, 1986 (Box 184, Folder 168)
  - Mayo, Dr. Charles W., 1947, undated (Box 184, Folder 169)
  - Mazey, Emil, 1948 (Box 184, Folder 170)
  - Mazowiecki, Tadeusz, 1989, undated (Box 184, Folder 171)
  - Mazurov, Kirill T., 1971 (Box 184, Folder 172)
  - Mboya, Tom, 1957-1960 (Box 184, Folder 173)
  - McBride, Lloyd, 1976 (Box 184, Folder 174)
  - McCall, Thomas, 1968-1971 (Box 184, Folder 175)
  - McCarren, Pat, undated (Box 184, Folder 176)
  - McCarthy, Eugene J., 1960-1968, undated (Box 184, Folder 177)
  - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1950, 1954, undated (Box 184, Folder 178)
  - McClellan Labor Rackets Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 184, Folder 179)
  - McCloy, John J., 1950-1961 (Box 184, Folder 180)
  - McCormack, John W., undated (Box 184, Folder 181)
  - McCoy, Hildy, undated (Box 184, Folder 182)
  - McCracken, Paul, 1970-1971 (Box 184, Folder 183)
  - McDonald, David J., 1959 (Box 184, Folder 184)
  - McDonald, Ian, 1982 (Box 184, Folder 185)
  - McElroy, Neil H., 1957 (Box 184, Folder 186)
  - McFarland, Sen. Ernest, 1951, undated (Box 184, Folder 187)
  - McGee, Gale, 1958, undated (Box 184, Folder 188)
  - McGinley, Phillis, undated (Box 184, Folder 189)
  - McGovern, George, 1968-1983 (Box 184, Folder 190)
  - McGuigan, Mark, 1980 (Box 184, Folder 191)
  - McHenry, Donald, 1979-1980 (Box 184, Folder 192)
  - McIlvane, Jane, undated (Box 184, Folder 193)
  - McIntyre, James, 1978-1979 (Box 184, Folder 194)
  - McKay, Douglas, 1952 (Box 184, Folder 195)
  - McKay, Robert, 1971 (Box 184, Folder 196)
  - McKeldin, Theodore, 1957 (Box 184, Folder 197)
  - McKinley, Bronson, 1986 (Box 184, Folder 198)
  - McKissick, Floyd, 1967, undated (Box 184, Folder 199)
  - McMahon, William, 1971 (Box 184, Folder 200)
  - McLuhan, Marshall, undated (Box 184, Folder 201)
  - McMahon, Brian, undated (Box 184, Folder 202)
  - McMath, Sidney, 1949-1950 (Box 184, Folder 203)
  - McMichael, Jack, undated (Box 184, Folder 204)
  - McNamara, Patrick V., undated (Box 184, Folder 205)
  - McNamara, Robert, 1960-1966 (Box 184, Folder 206)
  - McVeigh, Timothy, undated (Box 184, Folder 207)
  - Meany, George, 1951-1971, undated (Box 184, Folder 208)
  - Medaris, Maj. Gen. John B., 1957-1959, undated (Box 184, Folder 209)
  - Meguid, Esmart Abdul, 1987 (Box 184, Folder 210)
  - Meir, Golda, 1969-1971 (Box 184, Folder 211)
  - Menderes, Adnan, 1960 (Box 184, Folder 212)
  - Mendes-France, Pierre, 1953-1968 (Box 184, Folder 213)
  - Mendez-Montenegro, Julio Cesar, 1966 (Box 184, Folder 214)
  - Meng-Chi, Peng, 1962-1964 (Box 184, Folder 215)
  - Menninger, Karl, undated (Box 184, Folder 216)
  - Menshikov, Mikhail, 1958-1961 (Box 184, Folder 217)
  - Menzies, Robert G., undated (Box 184, Folder 218)
  - Mercader, Antonio, undated (Box 184, Folder 219)
  - Meredith, James, 1962-1967 (Box 184, Folder 220)
  - Merimee, Jean-Bernard, undated (Box 184, Folder 221)
  - Merriam, Robert E., undated (Box 184, Folder 222)
  - Merriam, W.E., 1972 (Box 184, Folder 223)
  - Mestiri, Ahmed, 1958, undated (Box 184, Folder 224)
  - Mexican Americans--Chicanos, 1969, 1973 (Box 184, Folder 225)
  - Mexico--Scenes, 1953-1962, undated (Box 184, Folder 226)
  - Meyer, Charles A., 1969 (Box 184, Folder 227)
  - Meyner, Robt., undated (Box 184, Folder 228)